datingsitesreviews.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Dating Sites Reviews

DatingSitesReviews.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information-gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

## Information that is Stored with an Account

When you create an account on DatingSitesReviews.com, you will need to provide a unique username and your email address. The email address is required to validate your account, support resetting your password if needed and to allow you to opt-in to content notifications such as new forum posts or comments. **Your email address is never displayed or made available through any page.** Your username and other optional profile information, such as, location, bio, signature are displayed with your forum posts, comments and on your profile page.

If you utilize the Social Site login feature, allowing you to log into our site using an existing social site login such as Facebook, Twitter, etc. we will also capture and store your unique identifier from said site, and if it exists your website URL. Before the login process is complete you will be required to login to the social site (if you are not already) and give permission for our site to use just this information. If permission is not granted, you will not be able to login into this site using the Social Site login.

## Information that is Automatically Logged

This site uses a visitor statistics package that logs the following information on each page access: userid, user_agent, IP, host, browser type, computing platform, date and time, page viewed, referer, request type, and query_string. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. This information is also gathered because we like to see what pages are being visited and how long visitors stay on the site. This helps us improve the user experience. **This information is not and will never be divulged to a third party unless required by law.**

Usage tracking data is kept a maximum of 1 month.

## Cookies

This site uses cookies to improve your experience and to provide us with information about how the web site is being used. Our cookies do not store personal information such as your name or email address. Cookies are required to log into the site.

Some third party tools also use cookies. Information about the third party tools we use can be found below.

### Third Party Cookies

We use Google Analytics at DatingSitesReviews.com to help us understand how the site is being used by visitors. Google Analytics reports this information without identifying individual users.

To find out how to prevent tracking by Google Analytics across all web sites, visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### Further Information About Cookies

If you wish to learn more about cookies and how to manage them, visit <https://www.aboutcookies.org/>.

## Public Forums, Reviews & Comments

This site makes reviews, comments, and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. While we do our best to ensure only appropriate information is posted, we cannot and do not assume responsibility for our user's postings. **All postings are property of their respective author.** Improper language is automatically censored by the system. All submissions are subject to our editorial control -- editorial changes will be indicated.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

## Data Quality/Access

This site gives users control over their user experience and content that they may have provided. Users can in some cases freely modify or delete any content they post for a limited time. Users have the ability to customize various aspects of the look and feel of the site.

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. DatingSitesReviews.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

## Right to be Forgotten

The way to be forgotten is simply to delete your user account on the site. All your submitted content, such as forum posts, comments, reviews, etc. will be anonymized making it extremely difficult and/or impossible to have anything linked back to you directly.

All user profile information such as username, email address and any other optional data such as location, bio, etc. will be deleted from our database immediately when the account is deleted.

## Limitation of Liability

DatingSitesReviews.com is not liable for any damages caused by any of the site content, whether directly provided by DatingSitesReviews.com its employees or not.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact the Admin.

Last Updated: Friday, August 31 2018 @ 11:26 am| Hits: 30,141 [](https://www.datingsitesreviews.com/staticpages/index.php?page=Privacy-Policy&disp_mode=print)
